OK, next we talk about the removal of chest and stomach transfer and the removal of the gastrointestinal tract
So, after the gastrointestinal tract is transferred to the gastrointestinal tract or transferred to other parts, we can do the gastrointestinal treatment
We can also do the rupture
Then we see this case is the form of the gastrointestinal tract
Then we can also do the form of the rupture
Let's take a look
So we see that the amount of this thymus after the transfer, we can also display it in the form of the ruptured
Let's first talk about the transfer to the gastrointestinal tract
First of all, we compare it with the round shape
The A-thymus is still retained
The pustular thymus is not there, but the gastrointestinal tract is increased
It must be that the pustular thymus is transferred to the gastrointestinal tract
There is no B-thymus, so the B-thymus is removed
So we remove B-thymus first
After απο méting, determine the location of the new thymus
And then the new thymus and the original
The pustular thymus and organ
Our basic procedure is to remove the scar and argues the area of the earwax
Then we remove the scar and argues the area of the earwax
Divide the round shape into the red part and the blue part of the neckline
Then we cross-stitch the neckline
Open the neckline
Then adjust the shoulder
This completes the neckline of our neckline
Okay, let's do it in 3D window
Still round shape
Then cut off the B-stitch directly
After cutting
We delete this amount
Then we choose these two lines
Then merge them
We can do symmetry later
You can also do it directly
Draw the front center line along the front center line
Then cut it off
Do half first
After doing half
Then open the symmetry
Okay, then the B-stitch will be deleted
After deleting
This new B-stitch is still our adjustment
So the adjustment is equal to the two edges of the shoulder
And it's all straight
Okay, what's next?
We can pull up a little bit
After pulling up a little bit
Delete this original B-stitch
Then check if the edges of the two B-stitches are equal
This is 118.3
This is also 118.3
Okay, it's completely identical
Then we press the Shift key
Choose these two B-stitch edges
Press the right mouse button
Rotate the B-stitch
At this time, we set the position of the new B-stitch
Then the new B-stitch must be compared with the style when setting
You see how much distance it is from the front center line
It's about a few percent of the whole neck
About one-third
Okay, this is the position of the new B-stitch
Okay, then the position of the new B-stitch
The position of the new B-stitch divides our circle into a small part
The big part is a part
Okay, we click the BP point
That is, the rotation center
Rotation center
Not the place where we finally receive the throat
Then all of our throat turns are around the BP point
So it must be the left-click to select the BP point
Then your mouse moves to
Generally speaking, when we rotate in this way
It's all about keeping the front center line unchanged
Then we choose
Or keep the big piece unchanged
Okay, then we left-click to select the small piece
Then move the mouse
At this time, our new B-stitch is balanced
New B-stitch
The new B-stitch is opened
After opening
Then we put it
This B-stitch
Pull it to the BP point at most
When actually receiving the throat
It's a little far away
There is a distance of one or two centimeters
Two or three centimeters
Okay, the bigger the volume
Then this B-stitch
Don't be too short
Try to get close to the BP point
If the volume is small
The B-stitch can be temporarily shortened
This is also the final shape effect
This requirement
Okay, we left-click to select the appropriate position
In this case, we will transform into a B-stitch
After turning into a B-stitch
Okay, let's put the A-stitch
Of course, you can also adjust the A-stitch directly at this time
We choose
Press the Shift key
Left or right
Choose the edge of the two-stitch
Pull directly down
Make it close to the BP point
Then press the Shift key
Select the left or right edge
Okay, right-click to cut
Okay, we
Of course, you don't have to cut it
But when we sew in 3D
It's easier to cut
Otherwise
The excess amount
It's not easy to deal with
Okay, so we're done
Half of the picture
Okay, the other half
We
Right-click
Left-click to select the front center line
Right-click the mouse
Right-click to open the edge seam line
Okay, that's it
Okay, I'm done with this picture
After that
Let's take a look at where
The A-stitch is not sealed
Seal it
Then the side seam
Remember to seal it
The shoulder line
See the Shift key
Two sections
One pair of more
Two sections to seal
Okay, after sealing
Let's open the 3D window
Open it
Show the arrangement
Okay
The arrangement is displayed
Then we check again
Is the seam line accurate
We
Ask you
Okay
At this time
We look again
You
The effect after the simulation
It's still the same as before I didn't do the A-stitch
The shape effect is also exactly the same
Okay
This is what we do
One is
Ah
A-stitch
We just said
It's the same
Okay
We can also make it a broken form
The A-stitch after transfer
Make it a broken form
Okay
So how do we break it
We
Okay
Make it a broken form
So how do we make it a broken form
How do we make it a broken form
Okay
Let's go back
And then history record
Okay
Let's go back to the original initial state
So what do we do
Because
Ah
The neck is going to be broken
So the process here
May be
More suitable
Common
Common process
Maybe add a rolling edge
Or something
Okay
Then we first
Left-click
Select
We left-click to select the neck
Right-click
Then select the internal line
Then this rolling edge
For example, you set it to 15
Or say
15 mm
Or 10 mm
This is based on its own design material
For example, we design
A one-centimeter
Such a
Then we cut it off
Okay
Cut off
Then we
Ah
The rest
And our
Just now
The way
We
Cut off
Okay
So we
Are doing the same
Ah
Yes
We
Speaker
Okay
we
In the
S
Tomato
Well
We
In the
S
The key
In the
S
To
Have
X
What
Is
X
What
Is
The
X
Zero
Hope
So
Now
Then
Let's
White
There are two ways to do this.
The first way is to move the
edge of the throat to a horizontal one.
Press and rotate.
At this time,
the position of the throat is the same as the position of the neck,
and it is in the form of a broken one.
So as long as it is in the position of the neck,
it will be fine.
It's about the same as in the style.
In addition,
the end point is not in here.
It is not the throat,
but the amount of transfer.
It is processed in the form of a broken one.
Therefore,
we can't pull the tip of the throat down to the BP point,
but it is the same as our neck.
At this time,
let's see.
It's transferred to this place.
This is all fabric.
The whole fabric is pulled in.
Well,
after this is done,
there is also a throat.
A throat,
let's see,
it is also transferred.
Let's cut it off.
It has also been transferred to the neck.
Let's choose two edges according to the shift.
Press the mouse button and right-click.
Choose to rotate the throat.
So this is the position of the throat.
It can be anywhere near here.
For example,
let's choose here.
Well,
in general,
the front center line,
the front center line remains the same.
So we must rotate this part here.
Okay,
move,
rotate.
After rotating,
the throat must also go directly to the top.
Okay,
this is rotated.
After rotating,
let's see.
This is a irregular shape.
What about this irregular shape?
We have to adjust it to a more round shape.
A round shape.
Of course,
we can delete the excess point directly.
After deleting it,
we can adjust it again.
How to adjust it?
Okay,
let's see.
After the adjustment is done, we can mix it with our face.
Then we can make it turn into a free curve point, and then we can delete some of the excess auxiliary lines with the hook tool.
After that, we can mix it.
You can use the line division tool.
Because it was a voice conversion just now, so after you open this edge division line, we will find that there are a lot of division lines that he recognizes as the edge of the voice.
You delete it.
Okay.
After we're done, we use the left mouse button to select the front center line, press the right mouse button, and then we open the edge division line symmetrically.
After opening it, then we sew the seam allowance, and then we sew the side seam, and then we sew the shoulder line.
At this time, you have to pay attention, because we just cut off a part of the round seam allowance.
So at this time, when we sew the back piece, it should be N to N free seam, more to more.
Okay.
Let's start from the back piece, that is, from the joint.
Let's start from the joint.
Press the Shift key.
This is the front line.
Enter.
After that, let's press the Shift key on the back line.
Select one piece, then select another piece, and then press Enter.
At this time, it will be sewed.
Don't forget.
This is the seam allowance.
Okay.
So after sewing this piece, then we open the arrangement point.
Then we cut the front piece.
Then we move the front piece over.
Okay.
After moving it over, we sew it.
After sewing, then we will see that the collar is relatively hard.
This is because of the hardening of our piece.
Okay.
We cut it out of hardening.
At the same time, in order for the collar not to be pulled to deform,
so we need to choose the line of this collar.
Open the digital editor.
Open the flexibility.
Then let its ratio be changed to 100%.
At this time, we re-model it.
Okay.
Let's see.
It will be better.
Some students will say that there will be a lot of folds.
This is because our particle diameter is relatively large.
If we increase the particle diameter,
the natural fold will come out.
We can also improve the quality.
Take a look.
Okay.
We see that this pattern doesn't agree with the one before we didn't make the fabric.
Some people say that this pleats is towards the front,
while this pattern is more uniform.
This is because the seam is related to the seam before us.
We didn't distinguish the difference of the fold size of this seam
when the whole seam of the whole piece is sewed.
So this is the problem.
How to adjust to be exactly the same with the style?
We can
take this part of the piece.
Okay.
We don't want it to have a fold.
We can divide the fold into several sections.
This section is the first section.
This section has a little bit of fold.
And then,
close to the front,
this fold is the largest.
At this point,
we can see that the fold is concentrated in the front.
Alright,
Let's see if there is any fold in the middle,
or only in the right corner.
So,
I can see that the fold is concentrated in the top left corner.
At this point,
this fold is completely considered a fold.
So,
I can see that the fold is concentrated in the bottom right corner.
This fold is concentrated in the top left corner.
Also,